A Finding Aid to the Paul Jenkins Papers, circa 1915-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, circa 1930-2010; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 9 Linear feet Box 1-9, Box 13
  - Griffin Golda, Lois, 1970-1978, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Gruneberg, Pierre and Monfort, Silvia, 1976-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Gruneberg, Pierre and Monfort, Silvia, circa 1993-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Grunig, Joseph and Dorothy, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Guerrand-Hermès, Hubert, circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Guibert, Gene and Sandal, circa 1954-1955, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Ga-Ger, circa 1962-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
    (Includes Helen Gee)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Ges-Gol, circa 1956-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - G, Miscellaneous: Goo-Gu, circa 1966-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    (Includes Peggy Guggenheim)
  - Hagen-Stubbing, Yvonne, circa 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hatje, Gerd and Ursula, 1963-1964, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hayashi, Hide and Makito, circa 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Hayman, Patrick, circa 1956-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Heckscher, August and Claude, circa 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Hélion, David and Rumney, Sandro, 1982-1987, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hélion, Fabrice, 1982-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hélion, Nicolas, 1983-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Henle, Fritz and Marguerite, circa 1980-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Henle, Maria, circa 1979-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Herbert, David, circa 1953-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Heschong, Naomi and Albert "Hesch", circa 1964-1965, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hess, Thomas B., circa 1961-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hirschfeld, Louise and Al, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hirshhorn, Joseph and Olga, 1971-1981, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Holden, Donald, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hosiasson, Philippe and Olga, circa 1956-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hudock, George, 1960-1966, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Ha-Hari, circa 1955-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    (Includes Pehr Hallsten, James Harithas)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Haro-Hen, circa 1963-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Her-Hod, circa 1944-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hof-Hoo, circa 1967-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - H, Miscellaneous: Hor-Hy, circa 1959-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - I, Miscellaneous, circa 1963-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Jackson, Martha, Martha Jackson Gallery, circa 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Jacot-Outie, Claude, 1981-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Jaffin, George M. and Janet, 1977-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Jaguer, Edouard and Simone, 1954-1955, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Jenkins, Burris, circa 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Jenkins, Georgia, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Jenkins, Hilarie, n.d.; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Jenkins, Louise, circa 1948-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Jenkins, Louise, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Jenkins, Louise, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Jenkins, Louise, 1961-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Jenkins, Louise, 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Jenkins, Louise from Esther Ebenhoe Jenkins, circa 1953-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Jenkins, Louise from Paul Jenkins, circa 1930-1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Jenkins, Louise from Paul Jenkins, circa 1944-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Jenkins, Louise from Paul Jenkins, circa 1953-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Jenkins, Louise from Paul Jenkins, circa 1953-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Jenkins, Paul A., 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Jenkins, Theresa "Nana", 1943-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Jenkins, William Burris, 1932-1944, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Jenkins Herrick, Nadyne (Fellers) and McCarthy, L.V. "Mac", circa 1945-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Jenkins Herrick, Nadyne (Fellers) and McCarthy, L.V. "Mac", circa 1964-1967, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Johnson, Buffie, circa 1950-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Jones, James and Gloria, 1969, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - J, Miscellaneous, circa 1954-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
    (Includes Maria Cooper Janis, Allen Jones)
  - Kanemitsu, Bunshi Paul, circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kanemitsu, Carole and Matsumi "Mike", 1962-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", 1953-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", 1954-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", 1965-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", 1972-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", 1981-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike", n.d.; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike" from Paul Jenkins, circa 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Kanemitsu, Matsumi "Mike" from Paul Jenkins, circa 1972-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Kaner, Sam, 1965-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Kaplan, Jacques, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Kasle, Gertrude, circa 1964-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Kaye, Harold, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Kinstler, Everett Raymond, 1987, 2000-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Kitchen, Lewis, Bryson, and John, Lewis Kitchen Realty, 1948, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Kluger, David, 1965-1967, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Knowles, Peter and Marguerite (Wickersham), circa 1954-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Koch, Edward I., 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Koenig, John Franklin, circa 1954, 1988-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kokubo, Akira, circa 1969-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Kralik, Erika, circa 1982-1984, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Kraus, Henry and Dorothy, 1982-1984, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Kriwet, Ferdinand, circa 1962-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Krol, Archbishop John Cardinal, circa 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Kroll, Lucy and Nathan, 1963-1967, 1981-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Kourilsky, Françoise, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Kumar, Ravi and Françoise, circa 1966-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Kumar, Ravi and Françoise, circa 1976-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Kumar, Viendra, circa 1964-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Kuniyoshi, Sara Mazo, 1953-1963, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Ka-Kat, circa 1966-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
    (Includes E. J. Kahn Jr.)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Kau-Ki, circa 1962-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
    (Includes Joseph P. Kennedy, Jean Kennedy Smith)
  - K, Miscellaneous: Kl-Ku, circa 1962-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Ladd, Parker, 1966-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Laming, Alan, The Art Gallery Magazine, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Lang, Jack, 1982-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lasker, Mary, circa 1962-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lassaw, Ernestine, circa 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Laughlin, Mortimer and Patricia, circa 1961, 1977-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Le Brocquy, Louis and Anne, circa 1978-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Leprette, Christian, 1978-1987, 1995-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Levenson, Milton and Frances, circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Libourel, André-Jean and Monique, 1980-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - London, George, 1964-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Looten, Emmanuel, circa 1958-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Lubasz, Harry, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Luxembourg, Daniella, Sotheby's, 1990-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - L, Miscellaneous: La-Las, circa 1953-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lau-Lel, circa 1960-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lep-Lic, circa 1965-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - L, Miscellaneous: Lin-Ly, circa 1965-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 53)
    (Includes Frank Lobdell)
  - La Fondation Maeght, 1986-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Mahoney, Florence, 1969-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Mailliard, Olivier and Catherine (Issert), 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Mallary, Robert W., 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Maloney, Daniel and Pieters, Christine, circa 1965-1986, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Mamou, Henry, circa 1984-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Martinoty, Jean-Louis, 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Mazursky, Paul and Betsy, 1978-1981, 1995-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Meadow, Lynne, 1985-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Melzac, Vincent, 1973-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Merrill, Tony, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Dorothy, The Museum of Modern Art, 1955-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Joan, circa 1957-1959, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mitterrand, François and Danielle, 1985-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Morgan, Barbara, 1975-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Morris, Mary, circa 1946-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mottel, Syeus, 1970, 1980-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mourlot, Eric, circa 1984-1985, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Muensterberger, Warner, circa 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mullen, Judy and Bob, circa 1960-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Müller, Horst, Galerie Müller, 1959-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Munsing, Juliana and Stefan, circa 1959-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - M, Miscellaneous: Ma-Marl, circa 1960-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - M, Miscellaneous: Marq-Mc, circa 1943-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
    (Includes Charles Marq, Gregory Masurovsky, Paul and Linda McCartney)
  - M, Miscellaneous: Me-Mil, circa 1964-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - M, Miscellaneous: Min-Mor, circa 1961-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - M, Miscellaneous: Mos-Mu, circa 1950-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Nash, Tom John, circa 1963-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New York University, 1966, 1981-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Newman, Arnold, 1957-1968, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Newsweek, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Nordland, Gerald, 1973-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Nordness, Lee, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - North, Xavier, circa 1983-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - N, Miscellaneous: Na-Nel, circa 1964-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - N, Miscellaneous: New-Nu, circa 1964-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - O'Hara, Frank, 1959-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Olitski, Jules and Kristina, 1974-1989, 2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Oliveira, Nathan, 1971-1974, 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Osborne, Tim and Eleanor, circa 1960-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - O, Miscellaneous, circa 1965-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    (Includes Bengt Olson)
  - Parker, Ray, 1966, 1984-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Patterson, Kristen, 1987-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Patterson, Marjorie, circa 1940-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Patterson, Marjorie, 1972, 1981-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Patterson, Marjorie, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Pavia, Philip and Natalie (Edgar), circa 1959-1969, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Picasso, Paloma, circa 1968-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Pleasance, Donald, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - The Poetry Center, 1964-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Pollock, Charles and Sylvia, 1963, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Pompidou, Alain and Nicole, 1989-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Pompidou, Claude, circa 1978-1981, 1996-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Prat, Jean-Louis, 1994-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Prince, Frank, circa 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Prokopchuk, Nicholas, 1960-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - P, Miscellaneous: Pa-Pin, circa 1954-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48)
    (Includes Eduardo Paolozzi)
  - P, Miscellaneous: Pio-Pu, circa 1956-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 49)
    (Includes Lee (Krasner) Pollock)
  - Q, Miscellaneous, circa 1953-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Radigue, Elaine, 1973, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Raiser, William, 1971-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Ray, Tony, circa 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Reep, Edward, 1982-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Restany, Pierre, circa 1954-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Rewald, John, 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Rheims, Maurice and Lili (Krahmer), circa 1963-1965, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Riberto, Vallo and Velma, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rigaud, Jacques, circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Robles, Esther, 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Rosenberg, Alex and Carole, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Rosenthal, Halina and Bernard "Tony", circa 1966, 1981-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rosier, Michèle, circa 1963-1965, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - R, Miscellaneous: Ra-Rein, circa 1962-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 64)
    (Includes Herbert Read)
  - R, Miscellaneous: Reis-Rog, circa 1944-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
    (Includes Roger and Karen Reynolds, Alain Robbe-Grillet, David Rockefeller)
  - R, Miscellaneous: Rom-Ru, circa 1962-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sachs, A.M., circa 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sanchez, Thomas, 1982-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sandler, Irving, circa 1961, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sawyer, Kenneth and Julia (Randall), circa 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sawyer, Kenneth and Julia (Randall), circa 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sawyer, Kenneth and Julia (Randall), circa 1956-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Schmied, Wieland, 1963-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Schneider, Alan and Jean, circa 1981-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Schneider, Alan and Jean, 1983-1984, 1991-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Schultze, Bernard and Ursula (Bluhm), circa 1954-1959, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Schwartz, Nancy, circa 1963-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Seely, Robert and Marcia, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Seeman, Joan, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Selz, Jean, 1984-1989, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Silberstein, Richard and Muriel, 1964-1974, 1983-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Silverman, Linda, circa 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Singh, Serbjeet, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Slivka, Rose and David, circa 1963-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Kimber, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Louise, circa 1963-1973, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sondeborg, Kurt and Sylvie, 1959-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Spanier, Samuel, circa 1954-1957, 1981-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Spanier, Samuel, circa 1991-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Sperling, Marie, 1986-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Stamos, Theodoros, circa 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Steinberg, Leo, 1960, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Stevenson, John and Isabelle, 1988-1994, 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Strauss, Minka and Karl Hans, circa 1964-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Stubbing, N. Hayden "Tony", 1959-1963, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Sutton, Keith, circa 1960-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sutton, Keith, circa 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Sutton, Keith, circa 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Suzuki, Takashi, 1961-1964, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Svoboda, Patricia, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Sa-Sat, circa 1962-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
    (Includes Ole and Helen Sarvig)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Sax-Schr, circa 1953-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Schu-Sek, circa 1955-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 39)
    (Includes Jean Seberg, George Segal, Rena Segal)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Sel-Sh, circa 1955-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
    (Includes Peter Selz, Harry Shunk)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Si-So, circa 1954-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Sp-Ste, circa 1962-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - S, Miscellaneous: Sto-Sz, circa 1955-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 43)
    (Includes James Johnson Sweeney [Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum])
  - Takahashi, Yoshito and Hiromi, circa 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Tapié de Céleyran, François, 1954, 1972-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Tapié de Céleyran, Michel and Simone, 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Thalmann, Gérard, 1982, 1995-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Thwaites, John Anthony, 1957-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Tobey, Mark, circa 1954-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Tobey, Mark, circa 1954-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Trapp, Frank, 1969, 1983-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Trapp, Frank, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Trapp, Frank, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Trapp, Frank, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Trapp, Frank, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Trapp, Frank, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Tully, Judd, 1988-1996, 2003-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - T, Miscellaneous: Ta-Th, circa 1955-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
    (Includes Edgar Tafel, Liliane Thorn-Petit)
  - T, Miscellaneous: Ti-Ty, circa 1959-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    (Includes Kenneth E. Tyler)
  - U, Miscellaneous, circa 1954-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Verame, Jean and Lili (Krahmer), 1982-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Verame, Jean and Lili (Krahmer), circa 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Verdet, André, circa 1984-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Veyne, Paul and Estelle (Blanc), 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Veyne, Paul and Estelle (Blanc), circa 1989-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Vikram, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - V, Miscellaneous, circa 1954-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    (Includes Michel Valette, Bernar Venet, Esteban and Harriet Vicente, Peter and Deborah (Kerr) Viertel, Jean-Claude Villain)
  - Weiss, Édouard, circa 1987-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Weisz, Heinz, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Weitzenhoffer, Frances and Max, 1979-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - White, Randy Lee (Whitehorse) and Marina and Sara, circa 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Whittet, George, 1962-1967, 1982-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Wickersham, Ruby, circa 1945-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Wickersham, Ruby, circa 1954-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wiesel, Elie and Marion, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Winkelbauer, Stefanie and Eberhard, 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wittenborn, George and Joyce, 1956-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Woelffer, Emerson, 1968-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - W, Miscellaneous: Wa-Wein, circa 1954-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - W, Miscellaneous: Weis-Will, circa 1942-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
    (Includes Jenny Bell Whyte, Hermann Warner Williams, Jr.)
  - W, Miscellaneous: Wils-Wy, circa 1964-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Xuriguera, Gerard, circa 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Yoshida, Toshio, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Yunkers, Adja, circa 1955-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Y, Miscellaneous, circa 1964-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
    (Includes Jan Yoors, Jiro Yoshihara)
  - Zokeisha Publications, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - First Names Only Correspondence, circa 1961-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 36)